dealzon.com 2019-10-02

# Dealzon Privacy Policy

Loading....

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, and information volunteered by the consumer (such as survey information and/or site registrations). Private information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web pages and the quality of our service, and is not shared with or sold to other organizations for commercial purposes, except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * It is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.
  * We transfer information about you if Dealzon or Dealzon is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Dealzon will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

## Information Gathering and Usage

  * When you sign up for an account we may ask for information such as your name, email address, and location.
  * Dealzon uses collected information for the following general purposes: products and services provision, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, and research.
  * We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when users visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our site, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

## Cookies

  * A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive.

## Data Storage

Dealzon uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run Dealzon. Dealzon owns the code, databases, and all rights to the Dealzon application.

## Disclosure

  * Dealzon may disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas or when your actions violate the Terms of Service.
  * It may be necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities, including without limitation, fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or as otherwise permitted or required by law.

## Changes

Dealzon may periodically update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Dealzon primary account holder account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

## Questions

Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed via email to support at Dealzon.com or by mail at: Dealzon, 93 S. Jackson Street #6940, Seattle Washington 98104-2818.
